[
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_01_HakenstadtDoll",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_01_HakenstadtDoll_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Primrose_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13A_SQ_01",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_04 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_01_HakenstadtDoll_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_01_HakenstadtDoll_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_01_HakenstadtDoll_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_01_HakenstadtDoll_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_01_HakenstadtDoll_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_01_HakenstadtDoll_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_01_HakenstadtDoll_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_02_KrummholmTransmutations",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_02_KrummholmTransmutations_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Primrose_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13A_SQ_02",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13A_SQ_01",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_02_KrummholmTransmutations_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_02_KrummholmTransmutations_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_02_KrummholmTransmutations_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_02_KrummholmTransmutations_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_02_KrummholmTransmutations_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_02_KrummholmTransmutations_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_02_KrummholmTransmutations_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_03_FreeHazel",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_03_FreeHazel_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Primrose_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13A_SQ_03",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13A_SQ_02",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_03_FreeHazel_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_03_FreeHazel_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_03_FreeHazel_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_03_FreeHazel_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_03_FreeHazel_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_03_FreeHazel_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_03_FreeHazel_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_14_GetTorches",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_14_GetTorches_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Pyro_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_17",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_04 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_14_GetTorches_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_14_GetTorches_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_14_GetTorches_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_14_GetTorches_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_14_GetTorches_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_14_GetTorches_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_14_GetTorches_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_15_GetIlluminationEssences",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_15_GetIlluminationEssences_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Pyro_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_18",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_17 \u0026\u0026 (99C_MSQ_11 || 99_MSQ_34)",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_15_GetIlluminationEssences_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_15_GetIlluminationEssences_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_15_GetIlluminationEssences_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_15_GetIlluminationEssences_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_15_GetIlluminationEssences_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_15_GetIlluminationEssences_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_15_GetIlluminationEssences_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_16_NavarrosKitchen",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_16_NavarrosKitchen_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Pyro_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_19",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_18",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_16_NavarrosKitchen_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "WaterT1",
        "ItemRewardQty": 1,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_16_NavarrosKitchen_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_16_NavarrosKitchen_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_16_NavarrosKitchen_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_16_NavarrosKitchen_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_16_NavarrosKitchen_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_16_NavarrosKitchen_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_04_MonsterBounty",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_04_MonsterBounty_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_MonsterHunter_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_20",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_11 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_04_MonsterBounty_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_04_MonsterBounty_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_04_MonsterBounty_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_04_MonsterBounty_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_04_MonsterBounty_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_04_MonsterBounty_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_04_MonsterBounty_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_05_FindHunters",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_05_FindHunters_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_MonsterHunter_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_21",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_20",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_05_FindHunters_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_05_FindHunters_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_05_FindHunters_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_05_FindHunters_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_05_FindHunters_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_05_FindHunters_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_05_FindHunters_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_06_KarburgHunters",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_06_KarburgHunters_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_MonsterHunter_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_23",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_21",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_06_KarburgHunters_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_06_KarburgHunters_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_06_KarburgHunters_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_06_KarburgHunters_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_06_KarburgHunters_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_06_KarburgHunters_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_06_KarburgHunters_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_17_KillGators",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_17_KillGators_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_AnimalHunter_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_24",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_04 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_17_KillGators_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_17_KillGators_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_17_KillGators_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_17_KillGators_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_17_KillGators_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_17_KillGators_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_17_KillGators_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_18_KillBoar",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_18_KillBoar_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_AnimalHunter_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_25",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_24 \u0026\u0026 (99C_MSQ_07 || 99_MSQ_34)",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_18_KillBoar_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "CoatingBeastT4",
        "ItemRewardQty": 3,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_18_KillBoar_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_18_KillBoar_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_18_KillBoar_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_18_KillBoar_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_18_KillBoar_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_18_KillBoar_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_19_KillWolfPack",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_19_KillWolfPack_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_AnimalHunter_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_26",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_25 \u0026\u0026 (99C_MSQ_11 || 99_MSQ_34)",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_19_KillWolfPack_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_19_KillWolfPack_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_19_KillWolfPack_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_19_KillWolfPack_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_19_KillWolfPack_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_19_KillWolfPack_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_19_KillWolfPack_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_20_KillWolfLeader",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_20_KillWolfLeader_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_AnimalHunter_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_27",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_26",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_20_KillWolfLeader_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_20_KillWolfLeader_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_20_KillWolfLeader_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_20_KillWolfLeader_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_20_KillWolfLeader_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_20_KillWolfLeader_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_20_KillWolfLeader_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_07_StudyRuins",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_07_StudyRuins_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Architect_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_28",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99B_MSQ_11 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_07_StudyRuins_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_07_StudyRuins_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_07_StudyRuins_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_07_StudyRuins_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_07_StudyRuins_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_07_StudyRuins_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_07_StudyRuins_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_08_BridgeStones",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_08_BridgeStones_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Architect_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_29",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_28 \u0026\u0026 (99C_MSQ_02 || 99_MSQ_34) ",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_08_BridgeStones_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_08_BridgeStones_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_08_BridgeStones_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_08_BridgeStones_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_08_BridgeStones_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_08_BridgeStones_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_08_BridgeStones_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_09_AndrometusStones",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_09_AndrometusStones_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Architect_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_30",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_29 \u0026\u0026 (99C_MSQ_08 || 99_MSQ_34)",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_09_AndrometusStones_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_09_AndrometusStones_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_09_AndrometusStones_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_09_AndrometusStones_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_09_AndrometusStones_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_09_AndrometusStones_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_09_AndrometusStones_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_21_SwampPerfume",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_21_SwampPerfume_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_PerfumeAlchemist",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_31",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_11 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_21_SwampPerfume_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_21_SwampPerfume_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_21_SwampPerfume_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_21_SwampPerfume_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_21_SwampPerfume_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_21_SwampPerfume_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_21_SwampPerfume_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_10_FindSpouseBridge",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_10_FindSpouseBridge_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Antiquarian_01",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_32",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_02 || 99_MSQ_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_10_FindSpouseBridge_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_10_FindSpouseBridge_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_10_FindSpouseBridge_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_10_FindSpouseBridge_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_10_FindSpouseBridge_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_10_FindSpouseBridge_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_10_FindSpouseBridge_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_11_FindSpouseCanopus",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_11_FindSpouseCanopus_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Antiquarian_02",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_33",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_32 \u0026\u0026 (99C_MSQ_08 || 99_MSQ_34)",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_11_FindSpouseCanopus_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_11_FindSpouseCanopus_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_11_FindSpouseCanopus_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_11_FindSpouseCanopus_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_11_FindSpouseCanopus_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_11_FindSpouseCanopus_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_11_FindSpouseCanopus_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_12_FindSpouseAquaAcadia",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_12_FindSpouseAquaAcadia_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_AntiquarianSpouse_00",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_34",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_33",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_12_FindSpouseAquaAcadia_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_12_FindSpouseAquaAcadia_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_12_FindSpouseAquaAcadia_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_12_FindSpouseAquaAcadia_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_12_FindSpouseAquaAcadia_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_12_FindSpouseAquaAcadia_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_12_FindSpouseAquaAcadia_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "TRUE",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_13_SpouseReunion",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_13_SpouseReunion_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "13A_Antiquarian_03",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "13_Quest_35",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "13_Quest_34",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_13_SpouseReunion_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_13_SpouseReunion_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_13_SpouseReunion_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_13_SpouseReunion_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_13_SpouseReunion_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_13_SpouseReunion_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_13_SpouseReunion_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    },
    {
        "ObjectiveID": "13A_SQ_28_BearUrine",
        "Type": "Journey",
        "Difficulty": "",
        "DifficultyLevel": "",
        "MaxInfluenceLevel": "",
        "FlagPvp": "",
        "CanBeShared": "",
        "CanFastTravel": "",
        "Task": "13A_SQ_28_BearUrine_container",
        "NpcDestinationId": "9904_MSQ_Theophrastus",
        "ExclusiveTerritory": "",
        "AchievementId": "99_MSQ_28",
        "RequiredAchievementId": "99C_MSQ_05 || 99_MSQ_27",
        "RequiredFaction": "",
        "RequiredLevel": "",
        "SuccessGameEventId": "13A_SQ_28_BearUrine_success",
        "FailureGameEventId": "",
        "ProgressionReward": "",
        "ExperienceReward": "",
        "ObjectiveReward": "",
        "ItemRewardName": "",
        "ItemRewardQty": null,
        "ShouldResetOnFactionChange": "",
        "Repeatable": "",
        "CanBeAbandoned": true,
        "Title": "@13A_SQ_28_BearUrine_objective_title",
        "Description": "@13A_SQ_28_BearUrine_objective_desc",
        "PlayerPrompt": "@13A_SQ_28_BearUrine_start",
        "ObjectiveProposalResponse": "@13A_SQ_28_BearUrine_proposal",
        "InProgressResponse": "@13A_SQ_28_BearUrine_incomplete",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailablePrompt": "@complete_available_prompt_DEFAULT",
        "DestinationCompletionAvailableResponse": "@13A_SQ_28_BearUrine_complete",
        "ObjectiveCompletionResponse": "",
        "ObjectiveAcceptanceResponse": "",
        "HideIncompleteTurninMarker": "",
        "ORMReleaseEventTags": "",
        "ORMReleaseActiveOverride": "",
        "SkipReqAchievmentWhenInvalid": "",
        "EntitlementId": "",
        "QuestArcTag": "",
        "HideAvailableMapIcon ": ""
    }
]
